thanks for coming on such short notice
small fires I can put out on my own but
this is above my pay GD what's the
problem exactly fires literally also
they're finding out the kombucha's dirty
seawat well the timing worked out I just
wrapped up a w season who' you rep black
people all of them it was a really good
year listen babe babe babe stay in the
tent okay your Postmates will be there
in about 45 minutes it's some Purge
going on right now so lay low please hey
guys this is Vanessa I'm here to help oh
my God please us what to do let's all
just calm down okay we can fix this
you'll be my tracker first things first
I booked a new lineup for weekend two
Puddle of Mud String Cheese Incident the
floppy sandwiches even if the bands
don't show you're still honoring your
contract how the did this happen
you said we were going to be Legends bro
I have a drug problem you do not have a
drug problem every Festival has a first
year Kinks I was at Coachella back in 07
it was like a leppo out there oh his
live set is really sick everything was
accounted look
here
see yeah this is just a bunch of stick
figures with
erections look we can still turn this
thing around we'll spend weekend one as
a giant escape room experience in the
Bahamas a dude got eaten it's authentic
we'll say the other festivals are too
corporate and this is what Burning Man
was 20 years ago is there a way we can
spin this where if you don't like the
festival you're racist B homophobic
amazing I'll write it down next to the
dick okay let's put a leaky pipeline
through the middle of the festival
grounds like they did in Dakota people
love that do they have zika out there oh
I love zika we could just say it was a
group hallucination I love it I can't
I'm
sorry hey guys North Korea just launched
a nuke in
La there it
is bae you still
there so
lit